<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Peace in Mind</title>
    <link>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Peace in Mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 14:14:40 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://namkolo.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Webpack configuration</title>
      <link>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/webpack-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 14:14:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/webpack-configuration/</guid>
      <description>I always wonder how to setup webpack to build a frontend react app from scratch? At the first glance, I felt so terrible about its document. It looks so big !!! Lots of things to do. But anything can be learned by step by step method. So I divided that progress into sub steps that I can follow.
First step is really simple. Just compile and copy code in src to public/build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 14:14:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/books/</guid>
      <description> Reading is my habit &amp;lt;3 I love reading all kinds of books. I often read books before sleeping or starting a new day.
Near future  Learn to play go: The way of the moving horse Why - a guide to finding and using causes  Current Reading List:  Search Inside Yourself (80%) Zen and Japanese culture (50%) Jack Canfield&amp;rsquo;s Key to Living the Law of Attraction: A Simple Guide to Creating the Life of Your Dreams (65%) Sherlock Home (33%) Bạn Không Thông Minh Lắm Đâu (20%) Ba trụ thiền (25%) Ma thiên ký (5%)  2017  Bước Chậm Lại Giữa Thế Gian Vội Vã Lối sống tối giản của người Nhật Nhân tố Enzyme Thiền dành cho người bận rộn Gieo trồng hạnh phúc Muốn an được an Vũ trụ Sự An Ủi Của Triết Học Phát Huy Tiềm Năng Cùng NLP (Tập 2) 38 basic joseki 501 opening problems Graded go for beginner (vol 1 -&amp;gt; vol 3) Opening theory made easy The little go books Building microservices Scala for the impatient Đại chúa tể Vũ động càn khôn Vạn cổ chí tiên Thiếu gia bị bỏ rơi  2016  Ai Và Ky Ở Xứ Sở Những Con Số Tàng Hình (Tiểu Thuyết Toán Hiệp) Trò Chơi Hữu Hạn Và Vô Hạn Không Bao Giờ Là Thất Bại - Tất Cả Là Thử Thách Tìm Lại Cái Tôi Đã Mất 20 Giờ Đầu Tiên Con Đường Thăng Tiến Chiến thắng trò chơi cuộc sống Đấu phá thương khung Đấu la đại lục Tiên nghịch Cầu ma Thần Ấn Vương Tọa  &amp;lt;= 2015  Sống và khát vọng Làm chủ tư duy thay đổi vận mệnh Tôi tài giỏi bạn cũng thế Quy hoạch động Cấu trúc dữ liệu và giải thuật Cơ sở dữ liệu Tru tiên Thần điều đại hiệp Anh hùng xạ điêu Lộc đỉnh ký Thiên long bát bộ Phàm nhân tu tiên Hiệp khách hành Ỷ thiên đồ long ký Tiếu ngạo giang hồ  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenge With Draft JS (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/challenge-with-draftjs-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 18:46:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/challenge-with-draftjs-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In the part 1, I wrote about how to set up simple editor with draft-js. But it was not the end, I had to do more. My side project needed the editor with below features:
 Change text color Change font size / font family Support drag and drop images Emoji/Hashtag  Hmmm, I searched lots about those features on google. Lots of good library built on top draft-js supported them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenge with Draft JS</title>
      <link>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/challenge-with-draftjs-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 18:46:03 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/challenge-with-draftjs-part-1/</guid>
      <description>One week ago, I had to implement Rich Text editor as one of features in my side project. After searching, I found draft-js which supported react very well. It looked so cool. So I decided to integrate it with my project. During that integration and studying, I struggled lots - from setting a simple editor to adding more advanced features for it. It was a really amazing journey to acknowledge myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup react-hot-loader with Express</title>
      <link>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/fe-hmr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 22:50:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namkolo.github.io/posts/fe-hmr/</guid>
      <description> Introduction What we will cover Go ahead </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>